You hear me?
>> We can hear you, coach.
>> Okay. Um, after reviewing the tape, um,
I basically feel the same way I did last
night. Um, we've, you know, we've got to
clean up some things, really all three
phases. Uh, there were some good things
from our young guys, but not enough. and
we we've um you know, we'll go back to
the drawing board here and and work on
that. Um for information,
uh Pat uh Patrick is going to go to
Dallas um for a second opinion with Dr.
Cooper and we'll just see we'll give you
updates as we as we go from there.
Um, and then [clears throat] as far as
the other injuries go, I really don't
have anything to offer you right now.
We'll we'll talk about that later.
That time's yours.
>> We'll go ahead and start with Pete
Sweeney. Go ahead, Pete.
>> I said I I'll have a second if I can.
Um, just just in generally speaking,
this is the first time Patrick is going
to have to go through a long rehab. Just
knowing what you know about him, how do
you feel like he he would attack that
challenge? Yeah, I think just what you
said, he'll attack it and he uh just
like he does everything else. Um
there have been some pretty good
quarterbacks that have had the same same
injuries and they've done pretty well
after after they came back. So, um he'll
he'll get after it and he's got good
people here to rehab him and um you
know, he'll again he'll he'll be right
on top of all that. And then Chris Jones
mentioned last night just your message
of finishing the season strong. Um with
that said, uh how much can you use these
three games as an evaluation period for
for the younger talent on the roster?
>> Yeah, listen, every game you go into, I
mean, it can be yatsi and you want to
win. I I mean, we're in America here.
That's kind of what we do. So you you
want to go in to play your best and um
you know if the guys are available
they're going to play and they they know
that and they want to do that. So um you
know you you find out
>> we'll go next to Jesse Newell.
>> Hey Sid. I'll have a follow-up too. Uh
hey Andy. Uh I just wondered how much
have you been able to talk to Pat in the
last 18 hours or so after the injury?
>> Yeah, I've had a good visit uh with him
uh a couple different times.
[clears throat] So um
he's he's in a good place, you know, he
always feels like he let people down,
but then he he comes back and he he's
ready for the challenge ahead.
um you know, which is what's real right
now. He he's just got to get get through
>> [clears throat]
>> uh surgery, wherever it might be, and
then uh and then move on from there.
>> Great. And just given some time to
process for yourself now, just what are
your own thoughts and emotions kind of
knowing now the severity of the injury
that he, you know, suffered?
>> Yeah, look, um I know I know the process
of rehabing for sure. um he'll u he'll
get in there and I I know he'll come out
on the strong end of this thing, you
know, and then as we go here, we're
we're finding a lot out about out.
Um some of the young guys are having
opportunities to play. Uh we're going to
finish this season strong and with with
effort and then um you know, then you
get into the offseason. But I I there's
um you know it's I'm I'm always
optimistic about going forward and uh
you know Brett V does a heck of a job
with bringing players in as you can see
now by the guys that are in there
playing. So, and then it's, you know,
our responsibility to clean things up on
the coaching side of it and the players
to take responsibility on their end and
um finish finish these three games and
then and then uh whoever's still here
after um to retool it.
>> We'll go next to Serin. Go ahead Sarin.
>> Uh thanks Sydney. I'll have a couple uh
as well. Uh, coach, first of all, just
kind of you said if if they're if guys
are ready, they'll play. You also just
said there, you know, some young guys
have had a chance. I'm just curious,
what would be the reason to to not, you
know, since, you know, you're not going
to be playing in the postseason to not
go ahead and I mean, what's the the
thinking of not playing younger players
that are definitely under contract and
that maybe could get some of some
valuable experience?
>> Most most of them are already playing.
Okay. [laughter] So, that's a that's uh
the main thing. I mean, you know, it's
uh I've got to see what the injuries are
here and uh from this game and then go
from there. But most of the young guys
are having an opportunity in one phase
or another. You know, you only have so
many numbers in this thing that you can
play with. So, in the NFL, it's not
quite like college where you have 90
guys that you can just pick and choose
from. Yeah. And then I know the other
question about the offense, obviously
the injuries are playing a part of it,
but does it feel like, you know, it's
just been out of sync all year for
whatever reason that you guys, you've
had some moments where it's been really
good. You go back to the Raider game,
the Lion game, but a lot of times it's
feels like everyone's just kind of like
when you go deep, Pat's talking about,
"Well, maybe you should have checked it
down." When he checks it down, he says,
"Well, maybe I should have been
aggressive." Have you just felt like
you've been kind of out of sync on that
all year?
Well, when when you lose close games,
you you search for things and so because
you want to fix it and uh sometimes it's
a penalty here, sometimes it's a a
turnover here, some you know um u you
know a variety of things. I mean there's
it's always one little thing that
determines close games normally one or
two things and we've had our share of
those and you can't have those. I mean,
it's uh uh you know, it could be the
wrong play called the wrong play at the
wrong time. So, we've all got a piece of
this thing and uh you got to keep
striving to to fix it and then uh do
what you do what you have to do in the
offseason, but you finish finish these
games here striving to do better and
cleaning up some things. And
I I mentioned one of the positive things
is you get to see a lot of young guys
play out of out of it. and
[clears throat]
see what they're all about.
>> We'll go next to Sam McDow.
>> Hey Andy. Um, a couple things. I just
wonder, first of all, you mentioned that
Patrick is getting a second opinion. Is
Is that because you guys are still
analyzing whether there's damage beyond
the ACL?
>> Uh, no, but these guys normally do that.
So, on that, Sam, those guys get a
second opinion.
uh probably put it up as much as
probably over 90% of the guys do this
and that's just part of it and
[clears throat] that's what he's doing.
>> And then just throughout the the this
last, you know, decade plus, I mean, you
guys have been so good at building as
the season progresses and getting
better. What's the difficulty in doing
that midyear knowing that the rest of
the league's trying to do the same
thing?
Yeah, you've always you've always got to
continue to strive to build and add to
to the roster. Um, and then you've got
to um stay ahead of the the game as as a
coach. And so, um, and that's every
offseason. That's the challenge. Uh,
sometime sometimes when you're when
you're good for the period of time that
we've been doing well, you're not
picking very high in the draft. And you
know that's uh you you make things you
make things work. Nobody's done it
better than Brett has. And um uh being
able to keep everything afloat and then
still not spending a ton on the or you
know working in the free agency market
uh as much as a lot of people do. So
we've done um you know he's done a great
job of juggling all that.
>> We'll go next to Todd. Todd Lebo. Go
ahead Todd.
Hey coach, a couple of things. First
off, on on your guys that you guys put
out the the uh tweet that he had an ACL.
Did the initial diagnosis have mention
anything about a meniscus or anything or
did it just look like an ACL?
>> Yeah, it's just what they put out there.
You know, we try not to hide too much
from you, right? That's not our our
game. I try to keep it right up front
with you. So, that's the information
that they had and they put it out for
you.
And secondly, you haven't been through
being out of the playoffs in December in
a long, long time. What's this been like
for you this uh you know, this past 24
hours with that realization? And where
do you kind of go back to to figure out
how to go about this next few games?
>> Yeah, Todd, I mean, obviously I'm not
happy about it. I um neither is anybody
here. I mean, that's uh we strive for
for excellence. We try to do that every
year. Um, things happen though in this
league. I mean, it's uh there's a ton of
parody and sometimes you end up on the
short end of it and you you've got to go
back and look at things and that can be
healthy and we've got good people to do
that with and we've got a good nucleus
of players. So, we we've got to go back
and look at all of that.
>> Go next to Nate Taylor. We've got two
left.
Andy, uh, you guys don't have another
quarterback on the roster right now for
2026. So, how much of this next three
games is an audition for Gardenner
Mitchu and the possibility of having him
uh, maybe come back for next season?
>> Yeah, sure. I've got a ton of confidence
in Gardner. So, I mean, it's uh,
[clears throat] I've watched him play
with these other teams. He started in
the league. Our guys have confidence in
him. Um uh and then Chris Olukan behind
him uh will will work up there and Chris
has been with us for a while too. So I
think they're two guys that are guys
trust um in there and uh we'll play hard
for him.
>> We'll close it out with Todd Palmer. Go
ahead Todd.
>> Hey Andy. Um [clears throat] first I
want to clarify Dan, you're talking
about Dan Cooper, the Cowboys uh
physician down in Dallas is who he's
going to go see. Yeah. Yes, Dan Cooper.
>> Okay. And then second, um, given the
typical time recovery timeline for for
something like this, I know you're still
in the season, but
I mean, how does that maybe alter the
way you guys have to approach the the
offseason knowing that that Pat's not
going to be available to do the stuff
he's normally done, may not even ava be
available to start training camp, things
like that?
>> Yeah, we'll we'll cross that as we go.
Um, Brett thinks of everything. I mean,
he jumps in on it and he he's he's well
ahead of all of it. Um, so I I'm not I'm
not worried about it. Uh, that part of
it. And then Pat, you never know on
these rehabs how they go. Um I I just
know he's got good people that he he'll
be working with and I know how
aggressive he is on things and um you
know as long as the surgery goes well
and as expected then um you know I I
would expect a fairly quick recovery for
him um just because of those those
factors.
>> Thank you coach. That's all we have.
Okay, good.